<resources>
    <string name="app_name">TourGuide</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>
    <string name="category_places">Places</string>
    <string name="category_food">Food</string>
    <string name="category_stay">Stay</string>

    <string name="places_name_activity_1">gateway of india</string>
    <string name="places_location_activity_1">18.921883,72.835255?z=18</string>
    <string name="places_oneLineDescription_activity_1">The Gateway of India is a monument built during the 20th century in Mumbai City of Maharashtra state in Western India.</string>
    <string name="places_description_activity_1">The Gateway of India is a monument built during the 20th century in Mumbai City of Maharashtra state in Western India.
        It is located on the waterfront in the Apollo Bunder area in South Mumbai and overlooks the Arabian Sea. The structure is a basalt arch, 26 metres (85 feet) high.
        It lies at the end of Chhatrapati Shivaji Marg at the water\'s edge in Mumbai Harbour.
        It was a crude jetty used by the fishing community which was later renovated and used as a landing place for British governors and other prominent people.
        In earlier times, it would have been the first structure that visitors arriving by boat in Mumbai would have seen.
        The Gateway has also been referred to as the Taj Mahal of Mumbai, and is the city\'s top tourist attraction.</string>
    <string name="places_timings_acvivity_1">always open</string>

    <string name="places_name_activity_2">Marine Drive</string>
    <string name="places_location_activity_2">9.9826,76.2754?z=18</string>
    <string name="places_oneLineDescription_activity_2">Marine Drive is considered as the best pathway for an evening stride</string>
    <string name="places_description_activity_2">Marine Drive is considered as the best pathway for an evening stride.
        The sight of sparkling waters of the Arabian Sea and the amazing feeling of cold breeze caressing your hair
        along with a long array of restaurants offering mouthwatering snacks and drinks can make any low day bright
        again. Needless to say that these streets are a perfect hang out place for all age groups! For the elderly,
        Nana-Nani Park is an absolute haven and is quite a recent attraction. This is the perfect hangout spot once
        you are in the city of Mumbai. The 3 km long Marine Drive is a natural bay and also forms a portion of the
        famous skyline of Mumbai. It has access to some of the major corporate centers, recreation activities and
        also places of entertainment.
</string>
    <string name="places_timings_acvivity_2">always open</string>


    <string name="places_name_activity_3">Elephanta Caves</string>
    <string name="places_location_activity_3">18.963253, 72.931442?z=18</string>
    <string name="places_oneLineDescription_activity_3">Elephanta Caves is a natural attraction located on Elephanta Island near Mumbai,
        Maharashtra, India.</string>
    <string name="places_description_activity_3">Elephanta Caves is a natural attraction located on Elephanta Island near Mumbai,
        Maharashtra, India. Those include a group of Hindu and Buddhist caves, with plenty of sculptured carved or built from rocks.
        The statues are of various sizes, and some of them were more destroyed by the time compared to the others.
        Elephanta Caves have a long history and are very popular among the tourists and visitors of Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="places_timings_acvivity_3">always open</string>

    <string name="places_name_activity_4">Girgaum Chowpatty</string>
    <string name="places_location_activity_4">18.9543,72.8128?z=18</string>
    <string name="places_oneLineDescription_activity_4">Chowpatty Beach is one of the most famous beaches in Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="places_description_activity_4">Chowpatty Beach is one of the most famous beaches in Mumbai.
        Located in the heart of the city, this beach is most popular for its local delicacies which most people
        enjoy whenever they visit Chowpatty Beach. Watching the glorious sunsets from this beach is a sight worth
        seeing! This beach is a retreat from a tedious routine for many. Most people visit this beach to relax after
        a long, tiring day. People of all age-groups come here to enjoy the scenic beauty offered by the beach. The
        sea, adorned by its long stretch of white sand in addition to the magnificent sky above, is like a heavenly
        dream for anyone who visits this beach. One can find beach vendors selling balloons, toys and local dishes
        such as spicy raw mango, roasted peanuts and Mumbai fast-food (or chaats). Tourists who visit Mumbai make
        it a point to visit this beach to experience the peaceful and serene atmosphere. People come here with their
        friends and families to spend several hours on this relaxing spot. A stroll on Mumbai\'s Chowpatty Beach will
        guarantee you an experience of a lifetime.</string>
    <string name="places_timings_acvivity_4">always open</string>

    <string name="places_name_activity_5">Siddhivinayak Temple</string>
    <string name="places_location_activity_5">19.0169, 72.8304?z=18</string>
    <string name="places_oneLineDescription_activity_5">The Shree Siddhivinayak Ganapati Mandir is a Hindu temple dedicated to
        Lord Shri Ganesh.</string>
    <string name="places_description_activity_5">The Shree Siddhivinayak Ganapati Mandir is a Hindu
            temple dedicated to Lord Shri Ganesh. It is located in Prabhadevi, Mumbai, Maharashtra.
        It was originally built by Laxman Vithu and Deubai Patil on 19 November 1801.
            It is one of the richest temples in Mumbai.
            The temple has a small mandap with the shrine for Siddhi Vinayak ("Ganesha who grants your wish").
            The wooden doors to the sanctum are carved with images of the Ashtavinayak (the eight manifestations of Ganesha in Maharashtra).
            The inner roof of the sanctum is plated with gold, and the central statue is of Ganesha.
            In the periphery, there is a Hanuman temple as well.</string>
    <string name="places_timings_acvivity_5">always open</string>

    <string name="places_name_activity_6">Sanjay Gandhi National Park</string>
    <string name="places_location_activity_6">19.2298,72.8963?z=18</string>
    <string name="places_oneLineDescription_activity_6">Elephanta Caves is a natural attraction located on Elephanta Island near Mumbai,
        Maharashtra, India.</string>
    <string name="places_description_activity_6">Elephanta Caves is a natural attraction located on Elephanta Island near Mumbai,
        Maharashtra, India. Those include a group of Hindu and Buddhist caves, with plenty of sculptured carved or built from rocks.
        The statues are of various sizes, and some of them were more destroyed by the time compared to the others.
        Elephanta Caves have a long history and are very popular among the tourists and visitors of Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="places_timings_acvivity_6">8 am to 7pm </string>

    <string name="places_name_activity_7">Haji Ali Dargah</string>
    <string name="places_location_activity_7">18.9827,72.8090?z=18</string>
    <string name="places_oneLineDescription_activity_7">The Haji Ali Dargah is a mosque and dargah
        (tomb) located on an isletoff the coast ofWorli in Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="places_description_activity_7">The Haji Ali Dargah is a mosque and dargah (tomb)
        located on anislet off the coast of Worli in Mumbai.Lying as it does in the heart of the city;
        the dargah is one of the most recognizable landmarks of Mumbai.
        Situated at the end of a 500m causeway protruding into the Arabian Sea is the whitewashed Haji Ali Mosque,
        containing the tomb of a Muslim saint Haji Ali who is believed to have meditated on these very shores.
        The Haji Ali Dargah was constructed in 1431 in memory of a wealthy Muslim merchant,
        Sayyed Peer Haji Ali Shah Bukhari, who gave up all his worldly possessions before making a pilgrimage to Mecca.
        Hailing from Bukhara, in present-day Uzbekistan, Bukhari travelled around the world in the early to mid 15th century,
        and eventually settled in present-day Mumbai.</string>
    <string name="places_timings_acvivity_7">7 am to 10 pm</string>

    <!-- ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~  Food ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~`-->

    <string name="food_name_activity_1">Sizzlers at Kobe\’s, Girgaum</string>
    <string name="food_location_activity_1">geo:0,0?q=13/14,, Marina Mansion, S. V. P. Road, Chowpatty Sea- Face, Lamington Road, Hughes Rd, Gamdevi, Mumbai</string>
    <string name="food_oneLineDescription_activity_1">Reasonably priced keeping in mind the quantity that greets you.</string>
    <string name="food_description_activity_1">Reasonably priced keeping in mind the quantity that greets you,
        Kobe’s hasn’t changed throughout the years, serving lip smacking sizzlers with the same great taste.
        Walk in here to add some spice and sparkle into your mean for even the desserts are sizzling masterpieces.</string>
    <string name="food_timings_acvivity_1">7 am to 10 pm</string>

    <string name="food_name_activity_2">Vodka panipuri , Pratap Da Dhaba</string>
    <string name="food_location_activity_2">geo:0,0?q=Pratap Da Dhaba, Link Plaza, Next To Punjab and Maharashtra Bank, Oshiwara, Andheri West, Mumbai</string>
    <string name="food_oneLineDescription_activity_2">Something different for most of you to try.</string>
    <string name="food_description_activity_2">Something different for most of you to try,
        the Vodka Pani puri is still more of an unknown delicacy in Mumbai.
        The need for innovation got this gem of a dish to emerge in the Mumbai Street Food scene and
        even if you don’t try anything else, you must try this !</string>
    <string name="food_timings_acvivity_2">8 am to 10 pm</string>

    <string name="food_name_activity_3">Imbiss</string>
    <string name="food_location_activity_3">geo:0,0?q=14, Ben O Lil Haven, Waroda Road, Off Hill Road, Bandra West, Mumbai</string>
    <string name="food_oneLineDescription_activity_3">Imbiss is a cosy little place that is already packed with loyal customers</string>
    <string name="food_description_activity_3">Imbiss is a cosy little place that is already packed with loyal customers by 8 pm.
        They serve great food and was always a place known for the best beef on this side of town.</string>
    <string name="food_timings_acvivity_3">7 am to 10 pm</string>

    <string name="food_name_activity_4">Samosa with Chola at Guru Kripa , Sion</string>
    <string name="food_location_activity_4">geo:0,0?q=40, Guru Kripa Building, Road 24, Near SIES College, Sion, Mumbai</string>
    <string name="food_oneLineDescription_activity_4">Reasonably priced keeping in mind the quantity that greets you.</string>
    <string name="food_description_activity_4">Known as Mumbai’s most famous samosa, this dish is served with a gravy of chickpea
        and is tamarind-y in taste. Onion and coriander bits are sprinkled to garnish.
        A must try for those who love to experiment with Mumbai street food.</string>
    <string name="food_timings_acvivity_4">8 am to 9 pm</string>

    <string name="food_name_activity_5">Strawberry and cream (Seasonal) at Bachellor\’s, Charni Road</string>
    <string name="food_location_activity_5">geo:0,0?q= 45, Sattar Sea View,Chowpatty Sea Face, Dr. Purandare Road, Marine Drive, Chowpatty, Mumbai</string>
    <string name="food_oneLineDescription_activity_5">Reasonably priced keeping in mind the quantity that greets you.</string>
    <string name="food_description_activity_5">Even though the strawberry and cream is on the slightly expensive side ,
        it is totally worth it. The cream is fresh, the strawberries are fresher and you just cannot get enough of the delicacy.
        There are more options such as thick shakes,  other fruit creams and ice creams.
        Late Nighters swear by the Mumbai Street Food special that is Bachelorrs!</string>
    <string name="food_timings_acvivity_5">7 am to 12 pm</string>

    <!--~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~`Stay ~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~~ -->

    <string name="stay_name_activity_1">The Taj Mahal Palace Mumbai</string>
    <string name="stay_location_activity_1">geo:0,0?q=The Taj Mahal Palace Mumbai</string>
    <string name="stay_oneLineDescription_activity_1">Since it opened in 1903, the hotel has created its own unique history, hosting everyone from Maharajas and Princes to various Kings, Presidents, CEOs and entertainers.</string>
    <string name="stay_description_activity_1">Since it opened in 1903, The Taj Mahal Palace and Tower, Mumbai has created its own unique history. From Maharajas and Princes to various Kings, Presidents, CEOs and entertainers, the Taj has played the perfect host, supportive of their every need.
        Built in 1903, the hotel is an architectural marvel and brings together Moorish, Oriental and Florentine styles. Offering panoramic views of the Arabian Sea and the Gateway of India, the hotel is a gracious landmark of the city of Mumbai, showcasing contemporary Indian influences along with beautiful vaulted alabaster ceilings, onyx columns, graceful archways, hand-woven silk carpets, crystal chandeliers, a magnificent art collection, an eclectic collection of furniture, and a dramatic cantilever stairway.
        Over the past century, The Taj Mahal Palace and Tower, Mumbai has amassed a diverse collection of paintings and works of art and is a veritable showcase of artifacts and art of the era. From Belgian chandeliers to Goan Christian artifacts, the hotel incorporates a myriad of artistic styles and tastes. .</string>
    <string name="stay_timings_acvivity_1">Welcome 24x7</string>

    <string name="stay_name_activity_2">Trident</string>
    <string name="stay_location_activity_2">geo:0,0?q=C 56, G Block, Trident Road, Bandra Kurla Complex, Mumbai</string>
    <string name="stay_oneLineDescription_activity_2">Welcome to a world of stylish accommodation, fine dining and gracious
        hospitality in the heart of North Mumbai</string>
    <string name="stay_description_activity_2">Welcome to a world of stylish accommodation, fine dining and gracious
        hospitality in the heart of North Mumbai\'s new business district; Bandra Kurla Complex. The epitome of elegance and efficiency,
        Trident, Bandra Kurla is located only 20 minutes from the airport and is a perfect place to conduct business or explore the exciting
        nightlife in the city that never sleeps.</string>
    <string name="stay_timings_acvivity_2">Welcome 24x7</string>


    <string name="stay_name_activity_3">The Oberoi, Mumbai</string>
    <string name="stay_location_activity_3">geo:0,0?q= The Oberoi, Nariman Point, Mumbai</string>
    <string name="stay_oneLineDescription_activity_3">Offering impeccable style and modern convenience in equal measure, our rooms are beautifully furnished, ornamented with unique, modern art and equipped with the latest technologies</string>
    <string name="stay_description_activity_3">Offering impeccable style and modern convenience in equal measure, our rooms are beautifully furnished, ornamented with unique, modern art and equipped with the latest technologies.
        These bright, light filled spaces are among the largest accommodations offered by luxury hotels in Mumbai. Situated in an unrivalled position on Marine Drive, they afford unparalleled views across the ocean and shoreline. Opt for a room or suite with an ocean view and enjoy 24 hour in room dining, served by a personal butler, beside breathtaking vistas.
        Equipped with high speed WiFi access and served by a 24 hour personal butler, luxury accommodation at The Oberoi, Mumbai is designed to meet the needs of business and leisure travellers to the city.</string>
    <string name="stay_timings_acvivity_3">Welcome 24x7</string>

</resources>
